// Quiz Questions
export const myQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is the name of the main character in Alien",
    answers: {
      a: "Ellen Ripley",
      b: "Pennywise",
      c: "Freddy Krueger",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Ellen Ripley",
  },
  {
    question: "What year did the third Alien film release?",
    answers: {
      a: "1999",
      b: "1992",
      c: "1983",
    },
    correctAnswer: "1992",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the ship in the first Alien film",
    answers: {
      a: "Serenity",
      b: "Nostromo",
      c: "Millennium Falcon",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Nostromo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Complete this quote from Aliens; 'You know, Burke, I dont know which species is worse. You dont see them f*****g each other over for a goddamn _______.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Percentage",
      b: "Snack",
      c: "Profit",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Percentage",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first to die in Alien",
    answers: {
      a: "Parker",
      b: "Brett",
      c: "Kane",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Kane",
  },
  {
    question: "Who directed Aliens?",
    answers: {
      a: "Tim Burton",
      b: "James Cameron",
      c: "Ridley Scott",
    },
    correctAnswer: "James Cameron",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the androids name in Alien 4",
    answers: {
      a: "David",
      b: "Bishop",
      c: "Call",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Call",
  },
  {
    question: "Which character did Bill Paxton play?",
    answers: {
      a: "Hicks",
      b: "Hudson",
      c: "Gorman",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Hudson",
  },
  {
    question: "What gift did Ellen give to the Queen in Alien 4",
    answers: {
      a: "Immortality",
      b: "Birth",
      c: "Speech",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Birth",
  },
  {
    question: "Who designed the creature Xenomorph?",
    answers: {
      a: "Claude Monet",
      b: "H.R.Giger",
      c: "Pueblo Picos",
    },
    correctAnswer: "H.R.Giger",
  },
];
